Guide to the Stanford University Website Collection
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Centers and institutes, 2010-2012; Series 3
  - Stanford Center for Legal Informatics, 2011
    - 2012 Sep 19, codex20120919; 3.56 megabyte(s) (50 files in 5 directories)
  - Stanford Center for Professional Development, 2011-2013
    - 2011 May 18, 788 megabyte(s) (16,668 files in 143 directories)
    - 2012 Mar 9, scpd20120309; 66.6 megabyte(s) (1289 files in 129 directories)
  - Stanford Computer Forum, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Oct 24-25, forum201110; 895 megabyte(s) (2258 files in 110 directories)
    - 2012 Oct 19, forum20121019; 1751 megabyte(s) (3816 files in 134 directories)
  - Stanford Environmental Molecular Science Institute, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Oct 3, emsi201110; 677 megabyte(s) (87 files in 7 directories)
    - 2012 Oct 17, emsi20120917; 677 megabyte(s) (87 files in 7 directories)
  - Stanford Historical Society, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Jul 19, shs201107; 104 megabyte(s) (109 files in 23 directories)
    - 2012 Nov 6, histsoc20121106; 74.6 megabyte(s) (117 files in 26 directories)
  - Stanford Humanities Center, 2011-2013
    - 2011 Jan 5, shc2011-033; 675 megabyte(s) (1703 files in 68 directories)
    - 2012 Feb 9, shc20120209; 249 megabyte(s) (3186 files in 780 directories)
    - 2013 Feb 7, shc20130207; 297 megabyte(s) (4781 files in 938 directories)
    - Presidential Lectures in the Humanities and Arts, 2012
      - 2012 Aug 28, prelectur20120828; 298 megabyte(s) (2,507 files in 191 directories)
  - Stanford Humanities Lab, 2011
    - 2011 Jul 29, shl201107; 14.1 megabyte(s) (369 files in 56 directories)
  - Stanford Institute for Creativity and the Arts, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Oct 24, spodds201110; 100 megabyte(s) (210 files in 18 directories)
    - 2012 Feb 13, sica20120210; 169 megabyte(s) (3996 files in 513 directories)
  - Stanford Institute for Economic Policy Research (SIEPR), 2011-2013
    - 2011 Jan 4, siepr2011-029; 129 megabyte(s) (3677 files in 209 directories)
    - 2012 Feb 9, siepr20120209; 141 megabyte(s) (669 files in 62 directories)
    - 2013 Feb 8, siepr20130208; 125 megabyte(s) (801 files in 65 directories)
  - Stanford Institute for Higher Education Research, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Oct 4, siher201110; 5.07 megabyte(s) (97 files in 11 directories)
    - 2012 Sep 18, siher20120918; 5.04 megabyte(s) (99 files in 12 directories)
    - National Center for Postsecondary Improvement, 2012
      - 2012 Jul 31, ncpi20120731; 75.3 megabyte(s) (556 files in 83 directories)
  - Stanford Institute for Materials and Energy Science (SIMES), 2010-2013
    - 2010 Dec 16, simes2011-021; 5.23 megabyte(s) (153 files in 10 directories)
    - 2012 Feb 10, simes20120210; 7.15 megabyte(s) (154 files in 10 directories)
    - 2013 Feb 4, simes20130204; 99.9 megabyte(s) (661 files in 429 directories)
  - Stanford Literary Lab, 2011-2013
    - 2011 May 23, 50.2 megabyte(s) (64 files in 19 directories)
    - 2012 Apr 9, litlab20120409; 49.9 megabyte(s) (63 files in 19 directories)
    - 2013 Apr 4, litlab20130404; 7.35 megabyte(s) (57 files in 19 directories)
  - Stanford Live, 2011-2012
    Prior to June 2012, Stanford Live was known as Stanford Lively Arts.
    - 2011 May 17, live_2011-126; 307 megabyte(s) (646 files in 67 directories)
    - 2012 Mar 9, lively20120309; 265 megabyte(s) (697 files in 71 directories)
    - 2012 Jun 8, live20120608; 236 megabyte(s) (330 files in 56 directories)
  - Stanford Magnetic Resonance Laboratory, 2011-2013
    - 2011 Aug 5, smrl201108; 70.4 megabyte(s) (368 files in 58 directories)
    - 2012 May 9, smrl20120509; 132 megabyte(s) (355 files in 60 directories)
    - 2013 May 3, smrl20130503; 82.5 megabyte(s) (362 files in 62 directories)
  - Stanford Nanocharacterization Laboratory, 2011-2013
    - 2011 Aug 10, snl201108; 4.57 megabyte(s) (247 files in 113 directories)
    - 2012 May 17, snl20120517; 5.26 megabyte(s) (246 files in 14 directories)
    - 2013 May 6, snl20130506; 4.77 megabyte(s) (252 files in 13 directories)
  - Stanford Nanofabrication Facility, 2012-2013
    - 2012 May 17, snf20120517; 2867.2 megabyte(s) (4566 files in 1652 directories)
    - 2013 May 6, snf20130506; 3532.8 megabyte(s) (4032 files in 1789 directories)
  - Stanford Publishing Courses for Professionals, 2012
    The Stanford Publishing Courses for Professionals were discontinued in 2009.
    - 2012 Aug 29, publishing20120829; 423 megabyte(s) (233 files 60 directories)
  - Stanford Summer Theater, 2012
    - 2012 Oct 31, summertheater20121031; 54.9 megabyte(s) (146 files in 33 directories)
  - Stanford Yacht Research, 2011-2013
    - 2011 Sep 9, syr201109; 8.29 megabyte(s) (93 files in 10 directories)
    - 2012 Jun 7, syr20120607; 16.7 megabyte(s) (71 files in 10 directories)
    - 2013 May 20, syr20130520; 16.7 megabyte(s) (71 files in 10 directories)
  - Study of Language and Information, Center for the (CSLI), 2010-2013
    - 2010 Dec 17, 123 megabyte(s) (1759 files in 197 directories)
    - 2012 Feb 9, csli20120209; 203 megabyte(s) (1770 files in 197 directories)
    - 2013 Feb 4, csli20130204; 5.17 megabyte(s) (224 files in 65 directories)
  - Study of the Novel, Center for the, 2011-2013
    - 2011 May 23, 10.7 megabyte(s) (70 files in 6 directories)
    - 2012 Apr 9, novel20120409; 25.6 megabyte(s) (134 files in 10 directories)
    - 2013 Apr 4, novel20130404; 28.8 megabyte(s) (133 files in 10 directories)
  - Sustainable Development and Global Competitiveness, Center for, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Oct 5, sdgc201110; 112 megabyte(s) (388 files in 13 directories)
    - 2012 Sep 19, sdgc20120919; 149 megabyte(s) (760 files in 32 directories)
  - Synchrotron Radiation Lightsource, 2011-2013
    - 2011 Aug 31-Sep 7, ssrl201109; 13004.8 megabyte(s) (15,536 files in 1833 directories)
    - 2012 May 23, ssrl20120523; 13005 megabyte(s) (14,479 files in 1,966 directories)
    - 2013 May 8, ssrl20130508; 9482 megabyte(s) (12,722 files in 1594 directories)
  - Teaching and Learning, Center for, 2012
    - 2012 Jan 24, ctl20120124; 7.81 megabyte(s) (238 files in 48 directories)
  - Technology Ventures Program, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Sep 6, stvp201109; 941 megabyte(s) (2511 files in 176 directories)
    - 2012 Jun 5, stvp20120605; 288 megabyte(s) (2,783 Ffles in 201 directories)
  - Theoretical Economics, Institute for, 2011-2013
    - 2011 Sep 7, site201109; 701 megabyte(s) (1046 files in 167 directories)
    - 2012 Jun 5, site20120605; 449 megabyte(s) (744 files in 171 directories)
    - 2013 May 9, site20130509; 541 megabyte(s) 787 files in 189 directories
  - Theoretical Physics, Institute for, 2011-2013
    - 2011 May 17, sitp_2011-130; 16.7 megabyte(s) (119 files in 23 directories)
    - 2012 Mar 9, sitp20120309; 16.3 megabyte(s) (121 files in 26 directories)
    - 2013 Mar 7, sitp20130307; 16.3 megabyte(s) (94 files in 35 directories)
  - TomKat Center for Sustainable Energy, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Oct 24, tomkat201110; 105 megabyte(s) (100 files in 13 directories)
    - 2012 Oct 22, tomkat20121022; 94.7 megabyte(s) (102 files in 13 directories)
  - Turbulence Research, Center for, 2011-2013
    - 2011 Sep 7, ctr201109; 616 megabyte(s) (938 files in 29 directories)
    - 2012 Jun 6, ctr20120606; 305 megabyte(s) (966 files in 30 directories)
    - 2013 May 9, ctr20130509; 221 megabyte(s) (826 files in 27 directories)
  - Vincent Coates Foundation Mass Spectrometry Laboratory, 2012
    - 2012 Jul 30, mass20120730; 47.6 megabyte(s) (178 files in 4 directories)
  - Woods Institute for the Environment, 2010-2013
    - 2010 Dec 16, 484 megabyte(s) (2537 files in 220 directories)
    - 2012 Feb 9, woods20120209; 1269.76 megabyte(s) (3556 files in 259 directories)
    - 2013 Feb 4, woods20130204; 585 megabyte(s) (3441 files in 177 directories)
  - Yamamoto Group, yamamoto20120924; 41.5 megabyte(s)
    - 2012 Sep 24, yamamoto20120924; 41.5 megabyte(s) (252 files in 46 directories)
- Events, Series 4
  - Amy Blue Awards, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Jul 15, amy201107; 2.05 megabyte(s) (117 files in 19 directories)
    - 2012 Oct 24, amyblue20121024; 1.13 megabyte(s) (108 files in 19 directories)
  - Commencement
    - 2011 Jun 10, commence2011-162; 31.1 megabyte(s) (165 files in 69 directories)
    - 2012 Jun 12, commencement20120612; 1.53 megabyte(s) (182 files in 76 directories)
    - 2014 Jun 15, commencement20140615; 81 megabyte(s) (765 files in 121 folders)
  - Founders' Celebration, 2012
    - 2012 Oct 8, founders20121008; 15 megabyte(s) (57 files in 25 directories)
  - Parents' Weekend, 2011
    - 2011 Sep 12, parweek201109; 22.6 megabyte(s) (65 files in 12 directories)
  - The Roundtable at Stanford, 2012
    - 2012 Nov 28, roundtable20121128; 1.94 megabyte(s) (133 files in 36 directories)
  - Summer Session
    - 2012 Oct 31, summer20121031; 399 megabyte(s) (13,225 files in 12,915 directories)
  - TEDxStanford, 2013
    - 2013 Apr 3, tedx20130403; 46 megabyte(s)
  - Western Association of Schools and Colleges Reaccreditation, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Nov 5, wasc2011-159; 109.0 (132 files in 36 directories)
    - 2012 Nov 9, wasc20121109; 25.3 megabyte(s) (116 files in 36 directories)
- Publications, 2011; Series 5
  - Administrative Guide, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Jul 15, admin201107; 27.2 megabyte(s) (189 files in 3 directories)
    - 2012 Oct 24, adminguide20121024; 30.6 megabyte(s) (175 files in 3 directories)
  - Annual Report, 2009-2011
    - Annual Report 2009, 2011 Jan 4; ar_2009; 5.44 megabyte(s) (95 files in 11 directories)
    - Annual Report 2010, 2011 Jan 4; ar_2010; 6.49 megabyte(s) (106 files in 40 directories)
    - Annual Report 2011, 2012 Jan 5; ar_2011; 9.76 megabyte(s) (112 files in 34 directories)
    - Annual Report 2012, 2013 Jan 10; ar_2012; 1.57 megabyte(s) (112 files in 25 directories)
  - Common Data Set, 2012
    - 2012 Apr 9, cds20120409; 2.07 megabyte(s) (77 files in 9 directories)
    - 2012 Dec 6, cds20121206; 6.12 megabyte(s) (78 files in 9 directories)
  - Conflict of Interest website, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Jul 15, coi201107; 1.06 megabyte(s) (771 files in 18 directories)
    - 2012 Oct 26, coi20121026; 1.25 megabyte(s) (65 files in 19 directories)
  - Faculty Handbook, 2012-2013
    - 2012 Apr 9, facultyhand20120409; 5.75 megabyte(s) (71 files in 5 directories)
    - 2013 Apr 4, facultyhandbook20130404; 6.12 megabyte(s) (72 files in 5 directories)
  - Habitat Conservation Plan, 2012
    - 2012 Dec 10, hcp20121210; 303 megabyte(s) (438 files in 11 directories)
  - Multidisciplinary Teaching and Research, 2012
    - 2012 Jul 27, 85.9 megabyte(s) (451 files in 51 directories)
  - Online Learning at Stanford, 2012
    - 2012 Aug 28, online20120828; 2.5 megabyte(s) (108 files in 31 directories)
  - Parents' Guide, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Jul 20, paren201107; 26.6 megabyte(s) (285 files in 68 directories)
    - 2012 Nov 6, parents20121106; 19.7 megabyte(s) (200 files in 66 directories)
  - Parents' Newsletter, 2009-2013
    - 2009 Spring, Parents_Newsletter_2009_spring
    - 2009 Fall, Parents_Newsletter_2009_fall
    - 2010 Spring, Parents_Newsletter_2010_spring
    - 2010 Fall, Parents_Newsletter_2010_fall
    - 2010 Winter, Parents_Newsletter_2010_winter
    - 2011 Fall, Parents_Newsletter_2011_fall
    - 2011 Winter, Parents_Newsletter_2011_winter
  - Privacy at Stanford, privacy20120829; 0.85 megabyte(s) (75 files in 16 directories)
  - Stanford Bulletin, 2011
    - 2011 Sep 13, bulletin2011-2012; 156 megabyte(s) (909 files in 7 directories)
    - 2012 Sep 4, exploredeg20120904; 33.5 megabyte(s) (405 files in 352 directories)
  - Stanford Business, 2013
    - 2013 Apr 1, stanford_business20130401; 80.2 megabyte(s) (3737 files in 119 directories)
  - The Stanford Challenge Final Report, 2012 Feb 8; 32 megabyte(s) (964 files in 291 directories)
  - Stanford in New York City, 2011
    - 2011 Sep 14, nyc201109; 2.74 megabyte(s) (95 files in 23 directories)
    - 2012 Jan 5, nyc20120105; 4.06 megabyte(s) (105 files in 28 folders)
  - Stanford Facts, 2012
    - 2012 Jul 25, facts20120725; 4.31 megabyte(s) (106 files in 18 directories)
  - Stanford News Service
    - Online archive of news stories from 1997-2010, 2011 June 30; 1331 megabyte(s) (31,982 files in 1546 directories)
    - News stories from 2011, 2012 Apr 26; news_2011; 217 megabyte(s) (1825 files in 96 directories)
    - News stories from 2012, 2013 Jan 29; news_2012; 162 megabyte(s) (2292 files in 94 directories)
  - Stanford University Library News, 1991-2009; SUL_News20130320; 43.6 megabyte(s) (627 files in 248 directories)
    - 1991-1997
    - 1997-1999
    - 2000-2009
  - Trees of Stanford, 2013 Dec 11; trees20131211
  - Visitor Information, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Jul 18, visit201107; 42.7 megabyte(s) (333 files in 71 directories)
    - 2012 Nov 2, visitor20121102; 45 megabyte(s) (325 files in 73 directories)